Creating AI animation videos is easier
制作人工智能动画视频
than ever.
比以往任何时候都更容易。
But making good AI videos with
但制作出
consistent characters is hard. That's
角色形象前后一致的优秀人工智能视频很难。
why in this video I will break down all
所以，在这段视频中，我将详细讲解
the different techniques that all
所有
YouTubers have been gatekeeping from
YouTuber 一直以来对
you. So by the end of this video you
你们保密的各种技巧。 所以看完这个视频，你
should be able to make your own [music]
应该就能制作自己的[音乐]
AI animation. But first, let me show you
AI动画了。 但首先，让我举
an example.
个例子。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; I'm home.
我到家了。
Mommy is
妈妈
gone.
走了。   这
So that is just a preview of my AI
只是我的AI
animation video. I won't show you the
动画视频的预览。 我不会把
full thing. But there are four steps
全部内容都给你看。 但
that go into creating your own AI
创建自己的 AI
animation video. We will go over image
动画视频需要四个步骤。 我们将讲解图像
generation and storyboarding. I'll show
生成和故事板制作。 我将向
you how to get started with image to
您展示如何开始使用图像转
video. Then I'll show you how to use
视频功能。 接下来我将向您展示如何将
that for audio sync. And lastly, I will
其用于音频同步。 最后，我将
talk about the editing. 95% of what I've
谈谈剪辑方面的问题。 我向你们展示的内容中，95%都是
shown you is done through Higgsfield AI.
通过 Higgsfield AI 实现的。
If you want to try this out for
如果你想亲自尝试一下
yourself, I would recommend click on the
，我建议你点击
link in the description down below so
下方说明中的链接，这样
you can follow along with me. Okay, step
你就可以跟着我的步骤操作了。 好的，
number one, we have storyboarding and AI
第一步，我们有故事板和人工智能
image generation. Before you make any
图像生成。 在创作任何
story, you first got to have an idea
故事之前，你首先要有一个关于
what your story is about. So as soon as
故事内容的想法。 所以，一旦
you have your idea in the back of your
你有了想法
head, you need to start storyboarding.
，就需要开始绘制故事板。
We will do that with image generation.
我们将通过图像生成来实现这一点。
As soon as I have an idea about a story,
一旦有了故事构思，
I start with creating my characters. So
我就会开始创作人物角色。 所以，
these are the three characters that we
这就是我们
will be creating. We have this husband,
要创作的三个角色。 我们有丈夫，
then we have the wife, and then we have
然后是妻子，然后是
the kid. All of them are created super
孩子。 所有这些都可以
easily just through Nanobanana.
通过 Nanobanana 轻松创建。
Basically, what I did is I set a 3D
基本上，我创建了一个
animated young woman of around 25 year
25 岁左右的 3D 动画年轻女性形象
old, and then I just described what she
，然后描述了她的
looks like. So that's not the hard part.
外貌。 所以，难点并不在这里。
The only thing you got to make sure of
你唯一需要确保的
is that you use the same style. So in
就是使用相同的样式。 所以，在
this case, they are all 3D animation.
这种情况下，它们都是 3D 动画。
Then the next step is creating your own
接下来，你需要创建自己的
character sheet. Your character sheet
角色卡。 你的角色卡
will actually help you with getting the
实际上可以帮助你保持
consistency right. So I have made a
一致性。 所以我为
character sheet of each of my
我的每个角色都制作了角色卡
characters. As you can see, we have all
。 如你所见，我们有
kind of different angles. We have
各种不同的角度。 我们还
different close-ups of their face on
从不同角度拍摄了他们面部的特写镜头
different angles as well.
。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; And now we can start using this. If you
现在我们可以开始使用它了。 如果你
want to make your own character sheet,
想制作自己的角色卡，
you can do that as follow. You basically
可以按以下步骤操作。 你只需
go over to Nanobanana Pro or Nanobanana
打开 Nanobanana Pro 或 Nanobanana
2. Then you upload the image of your
2，然后上传你
character that you have. So here I
拥有的角色图片即可。 所以我把这
uploaded the image of the guy. And then
个人的照片上传到这里了。 然后，
you copy in this detail prompt that I
请复制我给你的这条详细提示信息
have for you. If you want to find this
。 如果你想找到这个
prompt, you can find it in my free
提示，可以在我的免费
school community. There will leave all
学校社区里找到。 我会留下
the prompts that I use, so you can do
我使用的所有提示，所以你可以
this at your own pace, and it's
按照自己的节奏来做，而且
completely free. So you have nothing to
完全免费。 所以你没什么可
lose. Basically, I'm adding in this
失去的。 基本上，我是在添加这个
prompt. Then we create it in 16 by 9 and
提示。 然后我们以 16x9 和 4K 的分辨率创建它
4K, and then you hit generate, and this
，然后点击生成，你
will get you something like this.
就会得到类似这样的结果。
After you've created the character sheet
当你像这样为所有角色创建好角色卡后
for all of your characters like this,
，就
then you can get started with making
可以开始制作
your images. To create an image, all you
图片了。 要创建图像，
have to do is you have to upload that
您只需将
character sheet [music] into Nanobanana,
角色表（乐谱）上传到 Nanobanana，
and then you can simply add in your
然后即可添加您的
prompt. And this is where you start
提示。 这就是你开始
experimenting, because creating images
尝试的地方，因为制作图像的
is cheap. So you want to make as many
成本很低。 所以你要尽可能多地制作
different images as possible, because as
不同的图片，因为
soon as you start making videos, that's
一旦你开始制作视频，成本就会
where it gets expensive. So start with
很高。 所以，先从
storyboarding your thing first. Get an
绘制故事板开始吧。
idea. For example, here I have a 3D
想个办法。 例如，这里有一个 3D
animated man in a dark suit and a loose
动画人物，身穿深色西装，肩上挎着一个宽松的
and tight
紧身
&gt;&gt; [music]
音乐
&gt;&gt; messenger bag on his shoulder standing
邮差包，站在
inside a warmly lit apartment.
一间灯光温暖的公寓里。
Basically, what I'm doing is I have my
基本上，我的做法是先塑造一个
character, then I have like some details
角色，然后添加一些
about him, then I describe the kind of
关于他的细节，最后描述
like action he's doing. So he's having a
他正在做的事情。 所以他一只
hand on the door as if he's just walking
手搭在门上，好像正要走进
in, looking into the room, and it is in
去，往房间里看，这是
Disney Pixar animation style. Now you
迪士尼皮克斯动画的风格。 现在
hit generate.
点击生成。
Make sure you're detailed with your
请确保你的
prompt. Describe exactly what you want
提示信息足够详细。 请具体描述一下你希望在
to see there. So that got me this
那里看到什么。 所以就得到了这个
result. And you want to be doing this
结果。 你需要
for each of your scene. Now the first
对每个场景都这样做。 现在
example that I showed you of making this
我向你们展示的第一个制作这种
image is an easy example. In a second I
图像的例子很简单。 稍后我
will show you more advanced example, but
会给你展示一个更高级的例子，但
basically, what you want to do is you
基本上，你要做的就是
want to describe what you want to have
描述你想
happen in your story. So I made a little
在故事中发生的事情。 于是我在 Figma 里创作了一个小
story here in Figma, and then I just
故事，然后就
started storyboarding inside of Figma.
开始在 Figma 里绘制故事板。
So I'm putting in images of what's
所以，我会
happening on each scene, so that I have
在每个场景中添加一些画面，以便
going before I start animating this. So
我在开始制作动画之前，对故事的走向有一个大致的了解。 以上
these are all the images that I made.
就是我制作的所有图片。
Let me now show you how to make another
现在让我来向你展示如何制作另一张
image that is a bit more complex. It
更复杂的图像。 虽然
didn't end up making the scene, but it's
最终没能成功，但
still good for you to learn how to make
学习如何制作类似的东西对你来说仍然很有好处
something like that. So for this shot
。 所以，在这个
where they handing out flyers of this
他们分发
woman that is missing, I [music]
失踪女子传单的镜头中，我（音乐）
essentially used three image references.
基本上使用了三个图像参考。
I first used a character sheet of my
我首先使用了主角的角色卡
main character here, then I used a
，然后使用了
character sheet of the kid, and then I
孩子的角色卡，最后
also used this image as the flyer that
还使用了这张图片作为
they are handing out. If you combine
他们分发的传单。 如果将
that with a simple prompt like this, a
这个与这样一个简单的提示结合起来，比如一个
wide centered shot at night, a father
夜晚的广角中心镜头，一位父亲
and his young son stand on a sidewalk
和他的小儿子站在人行道上，向
walking past. Basically, describe what
路过的行人分发传单。 简单来说，就是描述
you want to see. That's the main
你想看到什么。 这就是
takeaway I want to give you here.
我想传达给你们的主要信息。
I'm saying that the father is holding a
我的意思是，父亲手里拿着
stack of flyers and the boy holds a
一叠传单，男孩手里拿着一
smaller stack. A woman reaches out and
小叠。 一位女士伸出手，
the dad hands her a flyer. Basically,
父亲递给她一张传单。 基本上，
what we see happening here, you want to
我们在这里看到的情况，你想
try and put that in simple words so that
尝试用简单的语言来表达，以便
you and the AI understands what's going
你和人工智能都能理解
on on the scene. I added in some details
现场正在发生的事情。 我补充了一些细节，
that both the father and the son look
比如父亲和儿子看起来都很
tired and a bit sad.
疲惫，还有点悲伤。
And then also what I did is at the end
然后，我在
of my prompt, I added in that it needs
提示的最后补充道，它需要
to look like Pixar Dreamworks [music]
看起来像皮克斯梦工厂[音乐]
style 3D animation. Another important
风格的3D动画。
thing that you can add in here is adding
这里还可以添加一些
in details about the lights. For
关于灯光的详细信息。
example, in that opening shot, I have a
例如，在开场镜头中，我使用了
soft light going on. And here I want to
柔光。 我希望这里的
lanterns. Now this is pretty important,
路灯也能有同样的效果。 这一点非常重要，
because if you don't add in these
因为如果不添加这些
details, you could get something like
细节，你可能会得到类似这样的结果
this.
。
So for example, this animation
例如，这个动画
completely failed as we have our 3D
完全失败了，因为我们把 3D
animated characters mixed with like real
动画角色和看起来很真实的
looking characters and there's not
角色混在一起，结果却没有
animation. I mean, unless you're making
动画效果。 我的意思是，除非你是在制作像《
something like Garfield where you have
加菲猫》那样的作品，其中只有
like one AI animated character and the
一个 AI 动画角色，
rest is all realistic looking people,
其余都是写实的真人角色，
then you might want this, but this is
否则你可能想要这种效果。但这
not the case and this looks a bit
不是这种情况，
strange in my opinion. But overall, when
在我看来，这看起来有点奇怪。 但总的来说，在
generating images, those are generally
生成图像时，这些方法通常都很
cheap. So just make the best ones and
便宜。 所以，尽你所能做到最好，并且
make a lot of them, because you can make
多做一些，因为
mistakes now. You don't want to make
现在犯错也没关系。 在制作视频时，你肯定不想犯
these mistakes when you're generating
这些错误
videos. I want to show you one more
。 我想再给你们展示一张
image that I make, which I think is
我制作的图片，我认为这张图
important for you to understand how I
对于你们理解我是如何
made this. So this image where he's
制作这张图片的很重要。 所以，他看着这张他们合影的这张照片，
actually made by first making this. So
实际上是先拍了这张照片才拍成的。
this is the first image that I made. So
这是我制作的第一幅图。 所以
this is them taking a selfie, and that's
这是他们在自拍，
just using their both of their character
只是用了他们各自的角色
sheets with a prompt of them sitting in
卡，提示是他们坐在
a cinema with a bucket of popcorn
电影院里，面前放着一桶爆米花
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]，一边
&gt;&gt; watching a movie while he looks at her.
看电影一边看着她。
Then I used this, I downloaded this, and
然后我用了这个，我下载了这个，
then I put this inside of the prompt
然后我把这个放进了提示
box. Let me actually show you. So I
框里。 让我实际演示一下。 所以我
basically gave it this character sheet.
基本上给它设计了这张角色卡。
So I have this image, which is our
我有一张
character sheet, and then I have this
角色卡图片，然后我还有一张
image of them. And then what you can do
他们的照片。 然后你可以在
is inside of Higgsfield, you can tag
Higgsfield 中给
them. So what I did in my prompt is we
他们贴标签。 所以我的提示是，我们越过他的
look over the right shoulder as he holds
右肩，看到他
a printed photo in both hands in front
双手拿着一张打印好的照片举在身前
of him. And then I'm adding in the at,
。 然后我添加了 at，
and then I'm adding in image two. So
然后我添加了第二张图片。 所以，
that means that I'm referring to that
我指的是那张
image. So the AI understands that we're
图片。 所以人工智能明白我们指的是
referring to that image. So then I'm
那张图片。 然后我
adding in more details, and then I hit
添加更多细节，然后点击
generate. So that ended up getting us
生成。 所以最终就得到了
this result. The next step what you can
这个结果。 接下来，
do with this is you can click open in
您可以点击“
multi-shot, and here you can start
多镜头打开”，然后就可以开始从
making different angles of this video.
不同角度拍摄这段视频了。
So without having to prompt, you can
所以无需提示，您只需
just put this in here and it will
在此处输入此内容，它就会
generate multiple different angles. Not
生成多个不同的角度。 并非
all will be usable, but some of them are
所有都能用，但其中一些
quite good. So for example, this is
相当不错。 例如，这
quite good. I like this one. I like this
相当不错。 我喜欢这个。 我喜欢这个
one. And basically, you can click the
。 基本上，你可以点击
ones that you like, and then you can
你喜欢的图片，然后
upscale them. This is another easy way
放大它们。 这是另一种
to get multiple different angles easily
轻松获得多个不同角度的简单方法，
without putting in too much effort into
无需花费太多精力手动重新构图
reframing the camera manually. Again,
。 同样，
because we will be using image to video
因为下一步我们将使用图像转视频（
in the next step, [music] it is
音乐），所以
important that you first lay out the
首先要确定
foundation of what your story will be.
你的故事框架。
And this will evolve during this
而这种情况会在此过程中不断演变
process. Like that's happened to me. And
。 就像我遇到过这种情况一样。
you will go back even while generating
即使在生成视频的过程中，你也会返回去
videos to make more images. But at least
制作更多图像。 但至少
if you have a basic storyline, then you
如果你有一个基本的故事情节，那么你
have a bit of an idea what you want to
就会大致知道
have happen in the next scenes. And this
接下来的场景会发生什么。 这样
will also save you a lot of credits. Now
还能帮你省下很多积分。
step number two is creating your videos.
第二步是制作视频。
We will do this by using image to video.
我们将通过图像转视频技术来实现这一点。
I will show you three different
我将向你展示三种
techniques that I think you should
我认为你应该
master to make your own long AI
掌握的技巧，以便制作你自己的长篇人工智能
animation videos. The first technique is
动画视频。 第一种方法
quite easy. It is using start and end
很简单。 它使用了起始帧和结束
frame, and I use this all the time. For
帧，我一直都在使用这种方法。
example, if we take a look at this
例如，如果我们看一下这个
video, and if I show you how I made
视频，如果我向你展示我是如何制作的
this, is it's him coming through the
，那就是他走进
door.
门来。
But as you saw in my generation, all I
但正如你们在我这一代人中所看到的，我所看到的只是
had was this image of him already
他已经
standing in this room. Now what we can
站在这个房间里的画面。 现在，
do to have a bit more control over the
为了更好地控制
outcome is we can use start and end
结果，我们可以使用起始帧和结束
frame. So what I did is I used this as a
帧。 所以我把它当作
reference, and then I can literally tell
参考，然后我就可以简单地告诉
Nanobanana something simple like remove
Nanobanana 一些事情，比如移除
the guy and close the door. That's all I
那个人并关上门。 我就是这么做的
did, and just generate it, and then you
，生成它，然后你
will get something like this. So now I
就会得到类似这样的结果。 所以现在我
download this shot also, and now we're
也下载了这个镜头，现在我们要进入
going over to Kling 3.0. You can find
Kling 3.0 版本。 您可以在
this here in video, then Kling 3.0, and
这里的视频中找到它，然后是 Kling 3.0，
here we have start and end frame. So
这里我们有起始帧和结束帧。 所以
what you want to do is you want to
你要做的就是把
upload that frame right here. Then you
那一帧画面上传到这里。 然后，你
want to upload the second frame with him
可以上传他
walking through the door, and then you
走进门的第二帧画面，然后
can add in your prompt where you say
添加你的提示，
something like he grips the doorknob,
比如他说：“我回来了。”他握住门把手，
turns it, and he pushes through the door
转动它，然后推门而入。
while saying, "I'm home." He steps
他走进
inside and slides his hands from the
屋内，双手从门把手滑到
doorknob to the edge of the door looking
门边，向
into the room. Then you can pick your
房间内望去。 然后您可以选择要
duration of how long you want this to be
持续的时间
happening, and then you hit generate.
，然后点击生成。
And then you have your finished results.
然后你就得到了最终结果。
I'm home. I use this technique all the
我到家了。 我一直使用这种方法
time to get the exact result that I
来获得我
want. And this is far easier than having
想要的结果。 这比让
the AI speculate like what happened
AI
before or after that by not providing a
不提供最后一帧数据就去推测之前或之后发生了什么要容易得多
last frame. If you just edit your image
。 如果你只
with Nano Banana, you have way more
用 Nano Banana 编辑图片，就能更好地
control over the outcome. Then we have
控制最终效果。 接下来是
technique number two, scene
第二种技巧，场景
continuation. So, if we take the example
延续。 所以，如果我们以
of our guy entering the door, let's say
这个人进门为例，假设
we want to have one continuous take like
我们想要一个连续的镜头，
this where he not only walks through the
他不仅走进
door, but also the camera pans to the
门，而且镜头还向右摇移
right side, and then we see the kid on
，然后我们看到
the couch. Like this is called scene
沙发上的孩子。 这就叫做场景
continuation because we're essentially
延续，因为我们本质上是
into one by using start and end frame.
通过使用起始帧和结束帧将两个不同的场景合并成一个场景。
To make it look seamless, it's very
为了使画面看起来浑然一体，
important that you take the last frame.
拍摄最后一帧非常重要。
So, in this case, this guy [music] or
所以，在这种情况下，这个人（音乐）或者
even like this as we already had that as
像这样，因为我们已经把它作为
our last frame, and you take that last
最后一帧，你取最后一
frame, download [music] that, and use
帧，下载（音乐），然后把
this as a start frame in the next scene.
它用作下一幕的起始帧。
So, now if we go back to the image that
现在，让我们回到
we made, so I already made an image
我们制作的图片，我已经制作了一张图片，图片中
where we have the kid sitting on the
孩子
couch like this. And if I save this
像这样坐在沙发上。 如果我保存这张
image, then I use this as my last frame.
图片，那么我就把它用作最后一帧。
So, combined we have this as a start
所以，结合起来，我们得到这个作为起始
frame and this as [music] a last frame.
帧，这个作为（音乐）作为结束帧。
We put this again inside of Kling, and
我们再次把这个放进克林格的镜头里，
then we basically say, "A man closed the
然后我们基本上是说：“一个男人关上了
door. Camera turns slowly. Pans [music]
门。镜头缓缓转动。摇摄（音乐响起）
towards the kid." And then we hit
向孩子移动。” 然后我们点击
generate. And then if we stitch that
生成。 然后如果我们把这一幕
together with the first scene, then we
和第一幕拼接起来，我们就
have one continuous take.
得到了一个连续的镜头。
&gt;&gt; [gasps]
[倒吸一口凉气]
&gt;&gt; The transition between the scenes is
场景之间的过渡
gone. The third and last technique that
消失了。
you need to understand to make a
要制作出
good-looking image to video generations
美观的图像到视频的转换效果，你需要了解的第三个也是最后一个技术
is Kling 3.0 multishot. This is super
是 Kling 3.0 多重拍摄。
powerful for if you want to have one
如果你想让一
generation with multiple different
台设备拥有多个不同的
camera angles. [music]
拍摄角度，那么这个功能非常强大。  [音乐]
In this case, you can do this with two
在这种情况下，你可以使用两个
camera angles or even more than that.
甚至更多的摄像机角度来实现这一点。
Here's an example of what multishot
以下是多重拍摄的示例
looks likes. In one 9-second video, we
。 在一个9秒的视频中，我们
have three camera angles. And that is
有三个拍摄角度。 那是
because I use multishot right here. To
因为我在这里使用了多重拍摄功能。 为了向
explain to you how I made this, I used
您解释我是如何制作这个的，我使用了
Kling 3.0 Omni. And what you can do in
Kling 3.0 Omni。 在
here is you can upload different
这里，你可以上传不同的
elements. So, essentially how this shot
元素。 所以，这个镜头的拍摄手法基本上是这样的：
where we have the father tucking in the
父亲给
kid to bed. Then we have the father like
孩子盖被子哄睡。 然后我们看到父亲
sitting against the wall. And then we
靠墙坐着。 然后我们还
have a character sheet of the father
需要一张父亲的角色卡，
because this way we have the clothes
这样才能保证服装风格
consistent. And that is essential
一致。 这一点至关重要，
because we have the father moving in
因为在这个镜头中我们看到父亲在移动
this shot. So, we want to make sure that
。 所以，我们要确保
the AI understand what he looks like.
人工智能能够理解他长什么样。
Then we enable multishot right here, and
然后我们在这里启用多重拍摄，并
we add in three different shots. For the
添加三个不同的镜头。
first shot, we're going to put in the
第一个镜头，我们会放入
image reference, and then we're saying,
参考图片，然后说：
"A father tucks his young son into the
“一位父亲把年幼的儿子哄
bed. Gently brushes his hair. Both look
上床，轻轻地梳理他的头发。两人看起来都很
sad." Then for the second shot,
悲伤。” 那么对于第二个镜头来说，
essentially this means that you have a
这实际上意味着你采用了
different camera angle here. The father
不同的拍摄角度。 父亲
stands up, turns off the light, opens
站起身，关掉灯，打开
the door, and walks out into the
门，走到
hallway. The door slowly closes. I made
走廊里。 门缓缓关上了。 我把
this one a little bit longer, so I made
这个视频稍微加长了一点，大概有
this like 4 seconds long. And then for
4秒钟长。
last shot, I gave it the following
最后，我给它出了以下
prompt. I first tagged the image that
提示。 我首先标记了
we're using for this, so we're using
我们要使用的图片，所以我们使用的是
image two, and then I gave the prompt,
第二张图片，然后我给出了提示：
"The father leans against the wall
“父亲靠在
besides the door and slowly slides down
门边的墙上，慢慢滑下来
to sit on the floor." So, that is how
坐在地板上。” 这就是
multishot works. Now you click generate,
多重​​拍摄的原理。 现在点击生成，
and then you will have a video like this
你就会得到一个像这样的视频
one.
。   最终效果和
than the reference images, but in my
参考图略有不同，但我
opinion it's better because I wanted him
觉得这样更好，因为我想让他靠着
door, and he's sitting at the opposite
门边的墙坐着，而他现在却坐在
side of the wall. Because if we look at
墙的另一边。 因为如果我们看一下
our reference, we have him sitting here,
参考数据，会发现他原本是坐在这里的，
but the AI made him sit there. Doesn't
但人工智能让他坐在了那里。
matter, it still looks pretty good.
没关系，看起来还是很不错的。
Another way of how you can do this is
另一种方法是将
you can stitch together different shots
不同的镜头拼接在一起，
and have a little compilation of
得到
different images or different scenes. In
不同图像或不同场景的小合集。 在
this case, it worked perfectly for this
这种情况下，它完美地契合了这个
scene.
场景。
So, that is another way you can do this.
所以，这是另一种方法。
You could still generate this
您仍然可以单独生成此文件
separately. Works just as well. Might
。 效果一样好。
even give you more control, but Kling
Kling 3.0 Omni 甚至可能给你更多的控制权，但
3.0 Omni is a good tool to use if you
如果你手头
have multiple different references
有多个不同的参考资料，
laying around and you want to just make
并且只想用它们制作
one video out of it. Now that you
一个视频，那么它是一个不错的选择。 现在你已经
understand how to make your images, your
了解如何制作图像和
videos, there's one more problem that we
视频，接下来我们还
need to tackle, and that is what we're
需要解决另一个问题，
going to do in step number three, which
那就是音频同步，我们将在第三步中解决这个问题
is audio syncing. Now this video that I
。 我
just showed you doesn't have much
刚才给你看的这段视频并没有太多
dialogue. And that's also a thing a lot
对话。 这也是很多
of people tend to avoid when it comes to
人在
making AI videos because the lip sync,
制作 AI 视频时往往会避免的事情，因为口型同步和
the dialogue sometimes might sound off.
对话有时听起来可能不太对劲。
however. I will show you this clip right
不过，我已经找到解决办法了。 我这就给你播放这段视频
here. So, this is before I applied my
。 这是我使用
voice changer. And this is him coming
变声器之前的样子。 这是他回家的情景
home.
。
I'm home. Now if I were to generate a
我到家了。 现在，如果我生成
different scene where I have this guy
另一个场景，让这个人
talking again, like for example this
再次说话，比如像这样：“
Hey buddy, why do you look so sad?
嘿，伙计，你为什么看起来这么难过？”
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; Where's Mommy? I couldn't find her, Dad.
妈妈在哪里？ 爸爸，我找不到她。
She wasn't here when I woke up.
我醒来时她不在。
&gt;&gt; Then in each AI-generated video, you
然后，在每个人工智能生成的视频中，你的
might have a slightly different voice.
声音可能会略有不同。
No matter what prompting you do, this
无论你如何引导，这个
will always be the problem. [music]
问题始终存在。  [音乐]
And that is a thing that a lot of people
而这正是很多人
don't know how to solve. The best method
不知道如何解决的问题。
you can use to solve this is using a
解决这个问题的最佳方法是使用
voice changer. Now what you can do is if
变声器。 现在，你可以
you go over to audio inside of Hixfeld
进入 Hixfeld 的音频设置，然后
and you go over to change voice, then
选择更改声音，就
you can upload your clip right here. And
可以直接在这里上传你的音频片段了。
then you can pick a voice, and then you
然后你可以选择一个声音，然后
can hit generate. So, after I change the
点击生成。 所以，在我改变声音之后
voice, it sounds like this and it's
，听起来是这样的，而且在
consistent across both scenes.
两个场景中都是一致的。
I'm home.
我到家了。
Hey buddy, why do you look so sad?
嘿，哥们儿，你怎么看起来这么难过？
Where's Mommy? I couldn't find her, Dad.
妈妈在哪里？ 爸爸，我找不到她。
She wasn't here when I woke up.
我醒来时她不在。
&gt;&gt; To be honest, this works decently. I'm
说实话，这方法还算有效。 我
not going to say to you that this is the
不会告诉你这是
best method, and I'm not going to
最好的方法，我也不会对
gatekeep the best method from you. The
你设下最好的方法的门槛。
best method if you want to truly solve
如果想真正解决这个问题，最好的方法
this is using the voice changer in
是使用
Eleven Labs. Basically works the same
Eleven Labs 中的变声器。 基本原理
way. In my opinion, it's a bit better
相同。 在我看来，它更好一些，
and you have more variety of voices to
你可以选择的声音种类更多，
choose from including making your own
包括制作你自己的
custom voice. Okay, let's wrap this up
自定义声音。 好了，我们来把这个视频
into the packaging, and this is where
包装起来，而这正是
you will make the difference between a
区分
good and a bad video. So, step number
好视频和坏视频的关键所在。 所以，第四步
four is editing. For this, you can use
是编辑。 为此，您可以使用
any type of video editor that you want.
任何您想要的视频编辑器。
You can use CapCut, DaVinci. Both them
您可以使用 CapCut 或 DaVinci。 它们都是
are free options, or you can use
免费选项，或者您也可以使用
Premiere. I already have Premiere on my
Premiere。 我的电脑上已经安装了 Premiere，
PC as I'm using it for my YouTube
因为我用它来管理我的 YouTube
channel, so I'm using it in this case.
频道，所以这次我也用它。
Essentially what you want to do, like
基本上，就像
I've explained in that storyboard that
我在我们制作的故事板中解释的那样
we make, you want to lay out every clip
，你要做的就是把每个片段
[music] after each other, and then you
（音乐）依次排列，然后你
can apply a little bit of editing to
可以进行一些编辑，
make it look good. The only thing that
使它看起来更好。
I've done here is I've added a bit of
我在这里唯一做的就是
film burn in this clip, and I've made
在这个片段中添加了一些胶片烧灼效果，并让
them fade into each other to make it
它们淡入淡出，使之
look like he's having a flashback. Then
看起来像是他正在回忆过去。 另外，
another tip I want to give you, if you
我还想给你一个建议，如果你
have a lot of dialogue, Kling 3.0 tends
有很多对话，Kling 3.0
to have some issues with lip syncing.
在口型同步方面往往会有一些问题。
What I did in this clip right here, in
我在这段
this orange one, is I literally took the
橙色片段中所做的，就是把
vocals or the audio right here, and I
这里的歌声或音频稍微
moved them a bit earlier. So, this is
提前了一点。 这就是
the clip. I copied that, and I moved it
视频片段。 我复制了那段代码，并把它移到了
a bit before the actual audio. And that
实际音频之前一点。 这样一来
way, if we compare this, then you can
，如果我们对比一下，你就可以
see that in this one, I'm home. the lip
看出，在这张图中，我在家。
sync is a bit off compared to this one.
与这个版本相比，这个版本的口型同步有点问题。
&gt;&gt; I'm home. [music]
我到家了。  [音乐]
it comes to editing is adding in some
剪辑时最后需要做的就是添加一些
sound effects and some music to tie the
音效和音乐，使
whole thing together. And you can make
整个作品浑然一体。 你可以
these sound effects through any type of
使用任何类型的软件制作这些音效
software. Let's say you're using
。 假设你正在使用
Artlist, you can find your sound effects
Artlist，你可以在那里找到你的音效
there. If you're already having Eleven
。 如果你已经在使用 Eleven
Labs, then you can also with AI make
Labs，那么你也可以利用人工智能制作
your own custom sound effects. And in
自己的自定义音效。 至于
terms of music, you can even AI generate
音乐方面，现在甚至可以使用人工智能生成
music now, or you can use something like
音乐，或者可以使用像
Artlist.
Artlist 这样的工具。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; I'm home.
我到家了。
Mommy is
妈妈
gone.
走了。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
[applause]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; I'll give you the names of every
我会把
undercover agent in my network. Just
我们网络中所有卧底特工的名字都告诉你们。
don't hurt my family.
别伤害我的家人。   就这样
So, that's it. That's how you make your
。 这就是制作你
own AI animation videos. If you want to
自己的AI动画视频的方法。 如果你想亲自
try this out for yourself, I would
尝试一下，我
strongly recommend using a tool like
强烈建议使用像
Hixfeld. I will leave the link to
Hixfeld 这样的工具。 我会
Hixfeld in the description down below,
在下面的描述中留下 Hixfeld 的链接，
and I will also leave a link to my
我还会在下面的描述中留下我的
school community where you can sign up
学校社区的链接，你可以在那里
for free and see all of my prompts that
免费注册，并查看我
I used for these videos and all of my
为这些视频以及我的所有
other videos in the description down
其他视频使用的所有提示
below. [music] Make sure to click the
。  [音乐]
video that's on the screen right now if
如果
you want to learn how you can make
你想学习如何制作
realistic-looking AI images and videos
逼真的AI图像和视频，请务必点击屏幕上的视频
of yourself. Seriously, it's a good
。 说真的，这
video. Watch it.
视频不错。 看看。